<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidX</string>

    <!-- application labels -->
    <string name="main_desc">Why pay $999+ for the iPhoneX when you can get the same look for FREE!
		Behold, AndroidX. Enable your iPhoneX look today</string>
    <string name="enable_androidx">Enable AndroidX</string>
    <string name="disable_androidx">Disable AndroidX</string>
    <string name="enable_androidx_feature_info">Enabling this feature will add the iPhoneX Notch to
		your phone. Saves you from paying big bucks for an iPhoneX!</string>

    <!-- menu headers -->
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="setting">Settings</string>

    <!-- about -->
    <string name="follow_me">Follow Me:</string>
    <string name="copyright_year">Copyright %s, Leonard Tatum. All Rights Reserved.</string>
    <string name="about_desc">This app is 100&#37; free, created for the education, convenience
		and use of the public. There will never be in-app purchases or alternative paid versions
		of the app. To learn about other apps Leonard Tatum is working on, connect with him on social
		media or send him an email with your questions or comments. Cheers!</string>
    <string name="feedback_email">For feedback or support, contact\n Leonard Tatum at
		<a href="mailto:ljtatum@hotmail.com">ljtatum@hotmail.com</a></string>

    <!-- privacy -->
    <string name="privacy_desc">Leonard Tatum is committed to protecting your privacy and
	providing the best user experience possible. This is why data collected will never be sold
	or traded to others. \n\nInformation collected may be used to (i) remember information so
	you will not have to re-enter it during your session or the next sessions you are using the
	Service (ii) provide personalize content and information to you and others, which could
	include online ads or other forms of marketing (iii) provide, improve, test and monitor the
	effectiveness of our Service (iv) develop and test new products and features (v) diagnose or
	fix bugs and issues.</string>

    <!-- settings -->
    <string name="customize_preferences">Customize Your Preferences</string>
    <string name="settings_power_saving">Power Saving: %s</string>
    <string name="settings_draw_over_app">Draw Over App\nPermission: %s</string>
    <string name="settings_power_saving_info">Enabling this feature will run the Service while
		the app is open. This will conserve your overall battery life</string>
    <string name="settings_draw_over_app_info">Enabling this feature allows the aesthetic to
		work! Keep this enabled at all times</string>
    <string name="settings_enabled">Enabled</string>
    <string name="settings_disabled">Disabled</string>

    <!-- network -->
    <string name="check_network">Sorry for the delay. We\'re having trouble connecting.</string>

    <!-- dialog options -->
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
</resources>
